Avatar Intro 

WATER.
EARTH.
FIRE.
AIR.

Long ago the four nations lived together in harmony, but then everything changed when the fire nation attacked.

Only the Avatar, master of all four elements,  could stop them. But when the world needed him most, he vanished.

A hundred years passed, and my brother discovered the new Avatar, an Airbender named Aang. And even though his airbending skills are great, he has a lot to learn before he's ready to save anyone...

But I believe Aang can save the world!
